<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?><TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <!--ebb: Need to rewrite XSLT to calculate dates from start to end of term. Non XSLT solution: To begin for a new year, autogenerate a list of dates and days of week in Excel (start with manually entering the first week's dates, and add +7 to each; format as ISO dates. 
            Paste in template xml file and autotag day and week divs. 
            Then manually correct with holidays and Fall Break, etc.-->
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Autumn 2016 Syllabus: Fantasy and Romance</title>
            <author>Elisa E. Beshero-Bondar</author>

            <sponsor>The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg</sponsor>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>First digital edition in TEI, date: <date from="2016-08" to="2016-12">Fall
                  2016</date>. P5.</edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <authority>University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg</authority>
            <pubPlace>Greensburg, PA, USA</pubPlace>
            <date>2014</date>
            <availability>
               <licence>Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported
                  License</licence>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <p/>
         </seriesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Born digital.</p>
         </sourceDesc>

      </fileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text>
      <front>
         <div type="courseID" style="outer">
            <head>Fantasy and Romance</head>
            <p>Englit 1572</p>
            <div type="meetTimes">
               <p><hi rend="em">Autumn 2016:</hi> Classes meet M W 4:00 - 5:15 PM, 118 Powers
                  Hall</p>
              <!-- <p><hi rend="em">Course Website: <ref target="http://newtfire.org/19cBrit/">http://newtfire.org/19cBrit/</ref></hi></p>-->
            </div>
            <div type="CRN">
               <p>Course Enrollment and Electives Info: </p>
               <list>
                  <item>Englit 1572: course registration number: <idno>29088</idno></item>
                  <!--<item>Socsci 1031: 25980</item>-->
                  <item>Satisfies the LT General Elective Requirement at Pitt-Greensburg and an R (Research) requirement for the Digital Studies Certificate.</item>
               </list>
            </div>
            <div type="faculty">
               <head>Instructor:</head>
               <p>
                  <ref target="http://www.pitt.edu/~ebb8/">Elisa Beshero-Bondar</ref></p>
               <p>Office Hours (in FOB 204)</p>
               <list>
                  <item>Wed. 11:30 AM -12:30 PM</item>
                  <item>Tues. 2-4 PM</item>
                  <item>and by appointment.</item>
               </list>
            </div>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="description" style="main">
            <head>Course Description</head>
            <!--  <graphic url=""/>-->
            <p>This course in literary history spans a busy century in Britain from the 1790s to
               about 1900, a time of revolutionary transformation and rapid technological
               development. We’ll learn about the emergence of Britain’s Romantic Movement in its
               revolutionary historical context, and observe Romanticism’s lasting influence on the
               writers of the Victorian era, named for the long reign of Britain’s Queen Victoria.
               Writers of this time witnessed the development of public education systems and the
               transformation of publishing technology to accommodate increasing numbers of literate
               readers in England and across the expanding British empire. Aspiring poets and
               novelists vied with each other to reach larger and larger markets. Many British
               writers took seriously the idea that literature could help connect the rich and the
               poor, and their writings address very serious social issues of the rapidly
               modernizing nineteenth century. </p>
            <p>These writers still speak to issues of our times. They addressed controversies
               surrounding poverty, race relations, and women’s rights. They responded to scientific
               debates over geological discoveries, as well as new theories of sexual selection and
               survival of the fittest. They questioned humanity’s relation to nature, the way
               emotions influence thinking, and what might happen to Britons living among people of
               other cultures around the world. Over the next fifteen weeks, we will be discussing
               how nineteenth-century British writers challenged the social conventions of their
               times, and how they responded to the barriers of their time between wealth and
               poverty, men and women, Britons and foreigners, nation and empire, at a time when
               that empire stretched itself thin to span the world. Along the way we’ll consider why
               the "antique" ideas, images, structures, and stories of nineteenth-century Britain
               are still so appealing to many of us in the twenty-first century.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="objectives" style="main">
            <head>Objectives:</head>
            <list>
               <item>Learn the contexts of nineteenth-century British literary history, its writers,
                  genres, and movements </item>
               <item>Learn to read poetry and prose as a dialogue with past contexts and current
                  issues</item>
               <item>Enhance your comprehension of the course material by engaging in class
                  discussions, and by conducting your own conversation with the texts as you
                  read</item>
               <item>Research and write about literature in historical and cultural contexts</item>
               <item>Gain experience in preparing informational resources about literature on the public web</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="courseMtls" style="main">
            <head>Texts to Purchase:</head>
            <p>Our course texts are available at the campus bookstore as a shrink-wrapped package,
               containing two Norton anthology volumes, and a free Norton edition of Mary Shelley’s
               Frankenstein (a deal direct from the publisher): <hi rend="em">Package ISBN:
                  978-0-393-91364-4</hi> This contains: </p>
            <list type="numbered">
               <item>Norton Anthology of English Literature, 9th ed., Vol. 9D (The Romantic
                  Period)</item>
               <item>Norton Anthology of English Literature, 9th ed., Vol. 9E (The Victorian
                  Age)</item>
               <item>free Norton edition of Mary Shelley, Frankenstein, ed. J. Paul Hunter, 2nd.
                  edition</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="grading" style="main">
            <head>Grading:</head>
            <p> Your grade will be based on Class Participation/Quizzes (10%), Short Papers (total: 20%), Three Digital Annotation Projects (total: 35%), two Midterm Exams (worth 10% each), and
               one Final Exam (15%). At least 90% of the work for the course must be completed in
               order to receive a passing grade (C or above).</p>
            <div type="participation">
               <head>Class Participation and In-Class Exercises: (15%)</head>
               <p>This portion of your grade reflects the extent to which you attend class regularly
                  and take an active role in class discussion, contributing thoughtful questions and
                  observations based on the readings, as well as responding to my questions. It will
                  also include your performance on any announced and unannounced quizzes and group
                  exercises I may give in class. If you keep up with the readings listed on the
                  schedule, and come to class each day prepared to discuss them, you will certainly
                  do well with this component.</p>
               <p> ** Note: Your attendance is vital to this course and your achievement in it. You
                  may miss three classes for any reason without penalty, but your participation
                  grade will be reduced for additional unexcused absences. You’ll also be missing
                  information and perspective on the readings that will almost certainly affect your
                  performance on assignments and exams. If you miss class, try to keep in touch with
                  other members of the class to find out what you’ve missed and consult with me to
                  help you catch up and to be sure you understand the material. Please note that
                  quizzes and in-class activities cannot be made up outside of the classes you
                  missed. </p>
            </div>
            <div type="weekly">
               <head>Short Writings: (15%)</head>
               <p>This portion of your grade is based on short
                  (2-page) response papers, and/or discussion board posts.</p>
             <!--  OLD Material from Fall 2014: <p><hi rend="em">Vocab/Context Logs (WLs): </hi> Submit on
                  Courseweb a Log entry in which you compile and explain at least 3 to 5 unfamiliar
                  words and/or contexts. Instructions:</p>
               <list type="numbered">
                  <item>Identify and locate the word or context using a line number in a poem, or a
                     page, chapter, or section (for a web reading). Check the footnotes in your text
                     or glosses along the sides of the page. If there is no gloss or footnote, or if
                     these aren’t sufficient to understand the word or subject, record it in your
                     log to research further:</item>
                  <item>
                     <list>
                        <item>Find the most likely definition of words from the Oxford English
                           Dictionary (Pitt Digital Library Database) that fits the passage or
                           sentence from which you excerpted it. Provide what you think is the most
                           likely and appropriate definition, quoting the relevant passages from the
                           dictionary. </item>
                        <item>For an unfamiliar phrase or context, try searching in Credo Reference
                           (Pitt Digital Library Database) first before a Google search. Give a
                           clear explanation in your own words.</item>
                     </list></item>
                  <item>Reflect and comment on how this word or topic fits within the part of the
                     text it’s from: Consider its use in the surrounding grammatical unit
                     (sentence), or paragraph or passage. Could there be more than one way to read
                     this? Briefly explain. Logs must be your own individual work and must not be
                     duplicated by others in the class. (See the section on Academic Dishonesty and
                     Plagiarism below.) </item>
               </list>-->
               <p><hi rend="em">Response Papers (RPs): </hi> (typically 2 pages long) are designed
                  to help you grapple with some challenging dimensions of our course readings, and
                  should help you to strengthen your comprehension. They may also give you topic
                  ideas for the major papers. Response Papers should follow MLA formatting and
                  citation guidelines (as needed). Short writing assignments lose points for lateness.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="projects">
               <head>Digital Annotation Research Assignments (10%, 10%, and 15%, for a total of 35%)</head>
               <p>Over the course of the semester, you will work on three projects involving close analysis and research, applied as 
                  annotation to produce online editions of our course readings. You will work with digital annotation tools
                  to build web-based information resources of nineteenth-century literary texts available for public view, and produce a research paper to accompany your work as your major project for the class. 
                  Detailed assignments for each project will be distributed in class and on Courseweb. Late project
                  submissions will drop one grade notch (for example, from B to B-) for each day
                  late.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="exams">
               <head>Two Midterm Exams (10% each) and a Final Exam (15%):</head>
               <p>The exams may consist of essay questions, identifications of passages, and brief
                  responses regarding significant events and literary terms we have discussed in
                  class. The Midterm will cover material from the first half of the course. The
                  Final Exam, given during Finals Week, will have a comprehensive section, but will
                  focus on material from the second half of the course. </p>
            </div>
            <div type="scale">
               <head>Grading Scale:</head>
               <p>Grades are posted on Courseweb, and follow this standard scale: A: 93-100%, A-:
                  90-92%, B+: 87-89%, B: 83-86%, B-: 80-82%, C+: 77-79%, C: 73-76%, C-: 70-72%, D+:
                  67-69%, D: 60-66%, F: 59% and below. In taking the course on a S / NC (pass-fail)
                  basis, students must earn a C to receive Satisfactory credit. G grades
                  (incomplete) may be given only in conformity with the University of Pittsburgh at
                  Greensburg's Bulletin: <ref target="http://www.bulletins.pitt.edu/greensburg/upg-academicpolicies.htm">http://www.bulletins.pitt.edu/greensburg/upg-academicpolicies.htm</ref>.</p>
            </div>
         </div>

         <div type="policies" style="main">
            <div type="daily">
               <head>Classes and Readings:</head>
               <p>This class is fast paced with very challenging reading. To do well in this course
                  it is vital that you attend class regularly and keep up with the readings! <hi rend="em">Read all the material assigned before class on the day it is
                     scheduled</hi> so that you can discuss the material in class, raise questions
                  about it, and intelligently respond to my questions and comments. <hi rend="em">Stay alert for any changes to the class schedule</hi>, which I will announce
                  in class and online on Courseweb and e-mail. </p>
            </div>
            <div type="courtesy">
               <head>Classroom Courtesy:</head>
               <p>Our class is fast paced, and requires that we all be making the best use we can of
                  our in-person class sessions. Arriving late and leaving early disrupts the
                  important collective mental activity of class. So does in-class texting and
                  checking your cell phone. While class is in progress, talking disruptively,
                  leaving the classroom, texting or using a cell phone or computer, reading a
                  newspaper, or other distracting behavior will be actively discouraged, and may
                  result in a deduction in your Participation grade. Please respect what we do in
                  the classroom: attend class regularly, and come prepared to contribute your
                  questions and ideas.</p>
               <p><hi rend="em">When an assignment is due,</hi> I expect that you will carefully
                  edit and proofread your documents, and that you will turn in your assignments on
                  time at the beginning of class or by the posted deadline for Courseweb
                  assignments. If you need an extension, ask me courteously at least a day ahead of
                  time. Do not ask for an extension on or after the day the paper is due.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="integrity">
               <head>Academic Dishonesty and Plagiarism:</head>
               <p><hi rend="em">Plagiarism</hi> falsely represents another source’s words or ideas
                  as your own, and, if you commit plagiarism in this course, you will receive a
                  final course grade of F and be reported to the Vice President of Academic Affairs.
                  Representing the voice of another individual as your own voice constitutes
                  plagiarism, however generous that person may be in "helping" you with an
                  assignment. <hi rend="em">To avoid plagiarism,</hi> cite your sources whenever you
                  quote, paraphrase, or summarize material, or use digital images from any outside
                  source (including websites, articles, books, course readings, Courseweb postings,
                  or someone else’s notes). Turning in an assignment generated collectively under
                  the name of a single individual is considered plagiarism. When instructed to
                  collaborate on a project, project collaborators share collective authorship and
                  should identify themselves directly as a team. When using the "copy" and "paste"
                  features as you read and research, be sure that you are carefully marking that
                  these passages are unprocessed from their source, so that you know to process it
                  later. Forgetting to do so not only produces sloppy work but (whether you intended
                  it or not) results in a false representation. As long as you make a good faith and
                  clear effort to cite your sources, you will not be faulted for plagiarism, but
                  your work will be penalized if citations are inaccurate, unclear, or lack
                  important information. <hi rend="em">Cheating</hi> on exams or exercises will also
                  receive a final course grade of F and be reported to the Vice President of
                  Academic Affairs.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="online" style="main">
               <head>Online Policies: </head>
               <div type="courseweb">
                  <head>Courseweb (or Blackboard): </head>
                  <p>My announcements, changes to the course schedule, assignments + online
                     assignment submissions, some course readings, powerpoint notes, and review
                     guides for this class will be regularly posted to Courseweb. Login to Courseweb
                     using your Pitt userid and password (the same one you use for your e-mail). All
                     courses you’re enrolled in that have Courseweb materials should be listed.
                     Courseweb link: <ref target="https://courseweb.pitt.edu">https://courseweb.pitt.edu</ref></p>
               </div>

               <div type="submissions">
                  <head>Turning in Assignments: Courseweb Upload</head>
                  <p> Turn in your papers <hi rend="em">by electronic upload through Courseweb</hi>.
                     We will be using the <hi rend="em">SafeAssign</hi> feature built into Courseweb
                     as a stable, time-stamped electronic archive for your papers. <note>Note: In a
                        crisis situation, you may send your paper to me by e-mail as an attachment,
                        but you must follow up with me to be sure I received it, if you have not
                        received a response from me in 24 hours!</note>
                  </p>
               </div>

               <div type="email">
                  <head>E-mail Correspondence: </head>
                  <p>Send e-mail to me when you have questions or want to meet with me, but <hi rend="em">please identify yourself by name (first and last), and provide a
                        Subject Line</hi> when you do so. I prefer you <hi rend="em">do not submit
                        your papers to me by e-mail</hi>; see directions above for submitting
                     assignments in print and online. </p>
                  <p>Each student is issued a University email address (username@pitt.edu) upon
                     admission. This email address may be used by the University for official
                     communication with students. Students are expected to read email sent to this
                     account on a regular basis. Failure to read and react to University
                     communications in a timely manner does not absolve the student from knowing and
                     complying with the content of the communications. The University provides an
                     email forwarding service that allows students to read their email via other
                     service providers (e.g., Hotmail, AOL, Yahoo). Students who choose to forward
                     their email from their pitt.edu address to another address do so at their own
                     risk. If email is lost as a result of forwarding, it does not absolve the
                     student from responding to official communications sent to their University
                     email address. To forward email sent to your University account, go to
                     http://accounts.pitt.edu, log into your account, click on Edit Forwarding
                     Addresses, and follow the instructions on the page. Be sure to log out of your
                     account when you have finished. (For the full Email Communication Policy, go to
                        <ref target="http://www.bc.pitt.edu/policies/policy/09/09-10-01.html">http://www.bc.pitt.edu/policies/policy/09/09-10-01.html</ref>.)</p>

               </div>

            </div>



            <div type="disability">
               <head>Disability Services:</head>
               <p>If you have a disability for which you are or may be requesting an accommodation,
                  you are encouraged to contact both your instructor and the Director of the
                  Learning Resources Center, Dr. Lou Ann Sears, Room 240 Millstein Library Building
                  (724) 836-7098 (voice) or los3 at pitt.edu as early as possible in the term.
                  Learning Resources Center will verify your disability and determine reasonable
                  accommodations for this course.</p>
            </div>
         </div>

         <!--  <div type="resources"><head>outside resources, fun stuff of use or interest?</head></div>-->



   <div type="schedule">
    <div type="week" n="1">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-08-29">M 08-29</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-08-31">W 08-31</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="2">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-05">M 09-05</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
               <p><hi rend="em">Labor Day Holiday: No classes.</hi></p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign"/>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-07">W 09-07</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="3">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-12">M 09-12</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-14">W 09-14</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="4">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-19">M 09-19</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-21">W 09-21</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="5">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-26">M 09-26</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-09-28">W 09-28</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="6">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-03">M 10-03</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-05">W 10-05</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="7">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-10">M 10-10</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-12">W 10-12</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="8">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-17">M 10-17</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
               <p><hi rend="em">Fall Break: Monday classes meet on Tuesday this week.</hi></p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
       <div type="day">
          <head>
             <date when="2016-10-18">T 10-18</date>
          </head>
          <div type="inclass">
             <p>. . . .</p>
          </div>
          <div type="assign">
             <p>. . . .</p>
          </div>
       </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-19">W 10-19</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="9">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-24">M 10-24</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-26">W 10-26</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="10">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-10-31">M 10-31</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-02">W 11-02</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="11">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-07">M 11-07</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-09">W 11-09</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="12">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-14">M 11-14</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-16">W 11-16</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="13">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-21">M 11-21</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-23">W 11-23</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
               <p><hi rend="em">Thanksgiving Recess: No Classes.</hi></p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="14">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-28">M 11-28</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-11-30">W 11-30</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div type="week" n="15">
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-12-05">M 12-05</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div type="day">
            <head>
                <date when="2016-12-07">W 12-07</date>
            </head>
            <div type="inclass">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
            <div type="assign">
                <p>. . . .</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
      <div type="week" n="16">
         <head>Final Exam Period - December 12-17</head>
         <div type="day">
            <head><date when="2016-12-15">Final Exam Date: Thursday 12/15</date></head>
            <div type="assign">
               <p><hi rend="em">Final Examination: 1 PM in our classroom, 118 Powers Hall</hi></p>
            </div>
         </div>
      </div>
</div>

      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>